cardeasexml.com 2013-04-05

# Privacy

You have the right to know how CreditCall Ltd. will use Your personal information and it is important that You read the following information regarding Our use of Your personal information.

  1. Definitions

**"CreditCall/We/Us/Our"** means CreditCall and any subsidiary or associated companies.  
**"You/Your"** means the person viewing this information.

  2. Information which We obtain and hold now or at any time in the future, about You may be recorded, analysed, assessed, used and held by Us This information includes any information which relates to or comes from: 
    * information supplied by others and/or obtained by Us as a result of enquiries We make, such as third parties associated with You and licensed credit reference agencies; and
    * information, proposals, referrals, application forms or other dealings with Us; and
    * Your chosen products and services; the conduct of any agreement(s) and/or account(s) with Us, if any, including but not limited details of transactions.
The Information set out above may be used for the purposes set out below:  
 
  3. To consider any requests, proposals or applications You make for products or services and to assist in credit assessment and in the management of agreements and/or accounts. 

When considering an application We may carry out now or in the future a credit search with one or more licensed credit reference agencies. Licensed credit reference agencies will record details of each type of search We make whether or not an application proceeds. 

Please write to CreditCall Ltd, Merchants House South, Wapping Road, Bristol, BS1 4RW if You want to have details of those credit reference and fraud prevention agencies from whom We obtain information about You. You have a legal right to this information. 

  4. To enable Us to: 
    * service Your relationship with Us, update information about You; and
    * conduct, monitor, manage and analyse Our business, including the administration, development and improvement of Our products and services, now and in the future; and
    * for audit, compliance and regulatory reporting purposes; this may include the disclosure of Your information to auditors and, if required, to governmental and non-governmental regulators.  
 
  5. To assist in the tracing of debtors for the collection of outstanding debts, debt collection and in the detection and prevention of possible loss or fraud. 

In connection with these purposes, We may disclose information about You and Your relationship with Us others outside CreditCall, such as debt collection agencies, card protection service organisations, Our legal advisers and, where appropriate, to other financial institutions. 

  6. To allow Us to offer You other products and services, which We think may be of interest to You. Any such offers may be made by telephone, e-mail or mail.   
 
  7. We treat Your information as confidential, however, subject to any requirement from regulatory bodies and the law, We may disclose information about You and Your relationship with Us to others outside CreditCall in order to provide You with Our products and services including any related benefits and products and services. This may include any processing required by Us. 

If We transfer information about You to another country outside the UK, We will make sure that the information will be adequately protected to the same levels of protection as We are required to apply to information held about You in the UK. 

  8. We may link information about You between agreements and accounts and the other products and services You may have with Us. We may also link information about You with information about others.   
 
  9. We may also disclose information about You and Your relationship with Us to:  

    * any party, including its advisers, to whom We transfer or propose to transfer Our business;
    * any party, including its advisers, to whom We transfer or assign, or propose to transfer or assign, Our rights and obligations under any agreement with You;
    * others inside and outside CreditCall in such other circumstances where We are obliged to, or as the law permits, or where We have Your consent.  
 
  10. Information about You and Your relationship with Us will be held by Us on a computer database and/or in any other way and will be kept by Us for only as long as it is required or permitted by law.   
 
  11. You are entitled to a copy of the personal data held about You by Us, as provided for under the Data Protection Act. To receive this information please apply in writing with a payment of £10 to CreditCall Ltd, Merchants House South, Wapping Road, Bristol, BS1 4RW. You also have the right to require Us to correct any inaccuracies in Your information.  
 
  12. CreditCall reserves all rights not expressly granted.  

**CreditCall Ltd.   Registered Office: Merchants House South, Wapping Road, Bristol, BS1 4RW.  Registered Number 3295653.**

**IMPORTANT NOTICE**   
**Before entering this Site please take time to read our[Terms of Use](http://creditcall.com/legal.shtml).  By proceeding further You are deemed to have read and accepted our Copyright, Site Legal Notice and Privacy Policy.**

**  
****Using Cookies**

Cookies are pieces of information saved to your computer when you access certain websites and come in two forms "permanent" and "temporary".

**Internet Banking / Applications**

Cookies are a requirement for the following:

  * CreditCall WebMIS
  * Online application forms on the CreditCall Ltd. website
  * Identifying the link you used to find our site
  * Checking which browser you use so that we can make sure our site and services work well on your computer
  * Monitoring traffic throughout our websites

You need to enable your computer to accept cookies; if you are have problems accessing our service please check that cookies are enables (see below)

**No personal data is collected by cookies on the CreditCall website.**

You can enable/disable cookies by following the instructions below :

**To disable Cookies:**

If you're using **Internet Explorer 6.0 or 7.0** :  
Choose Tools, then   
Internet Options   
Click the Privacy tab   
Click on Custom Level   
Click on the 'Advanced' button   
Check the 'override automatic cookie handing' box and select Accept, Block or Prompt for action as appropriate.

If you're using **Firefox 2.0** :  
Choose Tools, then   
Options   
Click the Privacy icon

If you're using **Firefox 1.0 or 1.5** :  
Choose Tools, then   
Options   
Click the Privacy icon   
Click the Cookies tab

If you're using **Opera 8.0 or 9.0** :  
Choose Tools, then   
Preferences   
Advanced   
Cookies

If you're using **Opera 7.0** :  
Choose File, then   
Preferences   
Privacy

If you're using **Netscape 6.0** :  
Choose Edit, then   
Preferences   
Click on Advanced   
Click on Cookies

If you're using **Internet Explorer 5.0 or 5.5** :  
Choose Tools, then   
Internet Options   
Click the Security tab   
Click on Custom Level   
Scroll down to the sixth option to see how cookies are handled by IE5 and change to Accept, Disable, or Prompt for action as appropriate.

If you're using **Internet Explorer 4.0** :  
Choose View, then   
Internet Options   
Click the Advanced tab   
Scroll down to the yellow exclamation icon under Security and choose one of the three options to regulate your use of cookies.

If you're using **Internet Explorer 3.0** :  
Choose View, then   
Options   
Click on Advanced   
Click on the button that says Warn before Accepting Cookies.

If you're using **Netscape Communicator 4.0** :  
Choose Edit, then   
Preferences   
Click on Advanced   
Set your options in the box that says Cookies.
